[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Cairo"]}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "What is going on right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "going", "on", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "Well, what we see, Piers, is the army is fully deployed in the streets of Cairo.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "we", "see", ",", "Piers", ",", "is", "the", "army", "is", "fully", "deployed", "in", "the", "streets", "of", "Cairo", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Are the protesters right to see the army as the saviors, or could they possibly be misled here?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "the", "protesters", "right", "to", "see", "the", "army", "as", "the", "saviors", ",", "or", "could", "they", "possibly", "be", "misled", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Well, in the next few days, we'll see.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "the", "next", "few", "days", ",", "we", "'ll", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "In very simple terms, what do you think this protest is really about?", "question_tokens": ["In", "very", "simple", "terms", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "this", "protest", "is", "really", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "People want change.", "answer_tokens": ["People", "want", "change", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "How did his speech go down on the ground?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "his", "speech", "go", "down", "on", "the", "ground", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "It sounded like a lead balloon.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "sounded", "like", "a", "lead", "balloon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Mubarak"]}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "When you watched President Obama's speech this evening, reading between all the lines, and it was very carefully phrased, what do you thing the key messages were that were going back to President Mubarak?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "watched", "President", "Obama", "'s", "speech", "this", "evening", ",", "reading", "between", "all", "the", "lines", ",", "and", "it", "was", "very", "carefully", "phrased", ",", "what", "do", "you", "thing", "the", "key", "messages", "were", "that", "were", "going", "back", "to", "President", "Mubarak", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "The key message to President Mubarak, Piers, was not good enough.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "key", "message", "to", "President", "Mubarak", ",", "Piers", ",", "was", "not", "good", "enough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Mubarak"], "TIME": ["this evening"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "I mean, how bad could this get, and what are the implications not just for America, but for the world?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "bad", "could", "this", "get", ",", "and", "what", "are", "the", "implications", "not", "just", "for", "America", ",", "but", "for", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "It could get a whole lot worse, piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "could", "get", "a", "whole", "lot", "worse", ",", "piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "How do we get rid of a guy if he doesn't want to leave?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "we", "get", "rid", "of", "a", "guy", "if", "he", "does", "n't", "want", "to", "leave", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Well, the administration served notice today and voices from Congress are serving even tougher notice.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "administration", "served", "notice", "today", "and", "voices", "from", "Congress", "are", "serving", "even", "tougher", "notice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "And the key question is: what does President Mubarak do in the next 48 hours and how does the Egyptian army react if he refuses to yield power and the demonstrators stay on the streets?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "key", "question", "is", ":", "what", "does", "President", "Mubarak", "do", "in", "the", "next", "48", "hours", "and", "how", "does", "the", "Egyptian", "army", "react", "if", "he", "refuses", "to", "yield", "power", "and", "the", "demonstrators", "stay", "on", "the", "streets", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "John, Wolf, thank you so much for that.", "answer_tokens": ["John", ",", "Wolf", ",", "thank", "you", "so", "much", "for", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Where do you think this is going to end, Amir?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "think", "this", "is", "going", "to", "end", ",", "Amir", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "I think it will take some time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "will", "take", "some", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amir"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Have you got any way of working that out?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "got", "any", "way", "of", "working", "that", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "I can simply -- I can easily say the majority sympathize with the protesters even though they haven't participated.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "simply", "--", "I", "can", "easily", "say", "the", "majority", "sympathize", "with", "the", "protesters", "even", "though", "they", "have", "n't", "participated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "What's going to happen here, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "to", "happen", "here", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "I think this falls into the category of delusional.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "this", "falls", "into", "the", "category", "of", "delusional", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Is that, you think, the reality?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", ",", "you", "think", ",", "the", "reality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I think, to start it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "to", "start", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Alexandria"]}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RBR", ",", "DT", "DT", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "So, it's not much of a surprise, is it really?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "much", "of", "a", "surprise", ",", "is", "it", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Well, I think the slow developing situation, even the incidents that have marked this year, the explosion at promise in Alexandria, the beating and killing of a businessman earlier, all these were events that signaled that on top of the disconnect, trouble was brewing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "slow", "developing", "situation", ",", "even", "the", "incidents", "that", "have", "marked", "this", "year", ",", "the", "explosion", "at", "promise", "in", "Alexandria", ",", "the", "beating", "and", "killing", "of", "a", "businessman", "earlier", ",", "all", "these", "were", "events", "that", "signaled", "that", "on", "top", "of", "the", "disconnect", ",", "trouble", "was", "brewing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"], "LOCATION": ["Egypt", "Egypt", "Israel"]}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Or is it beginning to look like it's backfiring?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "beginning", "to", "look", "like", "it", "'s", "backfiring", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Well, I think the real history of American engagement in Egypt begins with Camp David and the Egyptian-Israeli peace agreement that was reached, and has helped preserve the peace in the middle east between Egypt and Israel.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "real", "history", "of", "American", "engagement", "in", "Egypt", "begins", "with", "Camp", "David", "and", "the", "Egyptian-Israeli", "peace", "agreement", "that", "was", "reached", ",", "and", "has", "helped", "preserve", "the", "peace", "in", "the", "middle", "east", "between", "Egypt", "and", "Israel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Is that your reading of this?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "reading", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Piers, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "If the aid does get shut down, how long could Mubarak continue in office, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["If", "the", "aid", "does", "get", "shut", "down", ",", "how", "long", "could", "Mubarak", "continue", "in", "office", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VB", "VBN", "RP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Oh, I think -- I think it will be very quick, because, of course, he's relying right now -- he's pulled the police back.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "it", "will", "be", "very", "quick", ",", "because", ",", "of", "course", ",", "he", "'s", "relying", "right", "now", "--", "he", "'s", "pulled", "the", "police", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "What are the global repercussions of what we're witnessing in Egypt tonight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "global", "repercussions", "of", "what", "we", "'re", "witnessing", "in", "Egypt", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "We're certainly seeing something that's very historic.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "certainly", "seeing", "something", "that", "'s", "very", "historic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "With what is going on and the turmoil that we're witnessing, is the peace treaty with Israel going to be a casualty here?", "question_tokens": ["With", "what", "is", "going", "on", "and", "the", "turmoil", "that", "we", "'re", "witnessing", ",", "is", "the", "peace", "treaty", "with", "Israel", "going", "to", "be", "a", "casualty", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Not necessarily.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "necessarily", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Biden"]}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "What's been the impact, do you think, of Vice President Biden's statement globally, and specifically to the Arab world?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "impact", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "of", "Vice", "President", "Biden", "'s", "statement", "globally", ",", "and", "specifically", "to", "the", "Arab", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Well, globally and specifically to the Arab world, I think they are very disappointed with the American language, especially Vice President Biden's language.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "globally", "and", "specifically", "to", "the", "Arab", "world", ",", "I", "think", "they", "are", "very", "disappointed", "with", "the", "American", "language", ",", "especially", "Vice", "President", "Biden", "'s", "language", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Do you think the Obama administration would support him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "Obama", "administration", "would", "support", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "I -- well, it may support him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "well", ",", "it", "may", "support", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran", "China"]}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "We've seen similar use of these sites in Iran and also in China.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "seen", "similar", "use", "of", "these", "sites", "in", "Iran", "and", "also", "in", "China", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 24 hours"], "LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Or are there always ways around this now?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "are", "there", "always", "ways", "around", "this", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Well, what happened in Egypt today, in the last 24 hours, seems to be unprecedented in the history of the Internet, the fact that basically all service providers were shut down.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "happened", "in", "Egypt", "today", ",", "in", "the", "last", "24", "hours", ",", "seems", "to", "be", "unprecedented", "in", "the", "history", "of", "the", "Internet", ",", "the", "fact", "that", "basically", "all", "service", "providers", "were", "shut", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Are you worried about that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "worried", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Not right now, because I think they have a lot to handle to worry about single reporters or single organizations.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "right", "now", ",", "because", "I", "think", "they", "have", "a", "lot", "to", "handle", "to", "worry", "about", "single", "reporters", "or", "single", "organizations", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "What are you making of what you're seeing on the ground here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "making", "of", "what", "you", "'re", "seeing", "on", "the", "ground", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "I think the police have always been violent, but we haven't seen it this way, and especially because we haven't seen this many people on the street at the same time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "police", "have", "always", "been", "violent", ",", "but", "we", "have", "n't", "seen", "it", "this", "way", ",", "and", "especially", "because", "we", "have", "n't", "seen", "this", "many", "people", "on", "the", "street", "at", "the", "same", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]